Alright, we've been talking about what it is that you're good at, what jobs are out there, what's available.
But now you have to take a look at what do you want to do.
And that may conflict with what you're good at, that may conflict with what jobs are available.
But, it's very important that you know what it is you want to do.
What are your values and how will your work enhance those values?
What do you want to do on a day to day basis that will bring you joy and satisfaction?
Now I know sometimes, you know, you just, you have to make money.
But in the long term picture of things, you never want to get locked into a job where you're going to be miserable.
We spend so much time at work.
So what is it that you want to do?
Do you want to work in a place where you can wear jeans and a t-shirt?
Do you want to work outside?
Do you want to work nights?
What would make you happy?
Know what would make you happy before you start sending out resumes to a job that won't.